A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Diane Van Wie, Series 34 FA373
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Meetings, Luncheons, and Dinners, 1958-1973; 06; 21 document box(es)
  - Luncheon Honoring Members of the State Committee, Hilton Hotel, New York City, June 10, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 1962)
  - List of Officers, Executive Committee and Members of the Republican National Committee, July 19, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 1963)
  - Informal Outing for Republican Members of the Legislature, Pocantico Hills, October 1, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 1964)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - Pocantico Hills, October 8, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 1965)
  - Joseph Wilson - John Hanes Luncheon - 812 5th Avenue, November 22, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 1966)
  - Cocktail Party for Peter and Polly Anderson, Executive Mansion, November 29, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 1967)
  - Congressional Delegation - Joint Emergency Meeting, St. Regis Hotel, New York City, December 3, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 1968)
  - Luncheon for the 26 Men Represented in the Special Section of December Fortune, 812 5th Avenue, December 13, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 1969)
  - Meeting of County Chairmen, Executive Mansion, December 15, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 1970)
  - Board of Regents Meeting - Red Room, December 16, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 1971)
  - Empire State Chamber of Commerce Luncheon - Mansion, February 2, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 1972)
  - National Governors' Conference 1972 Mid-Year Meeting, February 21-23, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 1973)
  - National Governors' Conference - Winter Meeting - Washington, D. C., February 22-24, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 1974)
  - Public Health Council Luncheon - Executive Mansion, March 6, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 1975)
  - Newsday Dinner at L'Auberge Des Fougeres, Albany, March 13, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 1976)
  - Court of Appals Reception, 6:45 PM - Executive Mansion, March 14, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 1977)
  - Meeting with President Nixon and New York State Narcotics Commissioners in Washington, DC, March 20, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 1978)
  - Cocktail Party in Honor of U Thant, 812 5th Avenue, March 23, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 1979)
  - Conference of Large City Boards of Education Meeting, New York State, April 14, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 1980)
  - Scott Commission Luncheon Meeting, Executive Mansion, April 17, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 1981)
  - Luncheon for Wilbur Mills, Executive Mansion, April 19, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 1982)
  - Labor Dinner, Pocantico Hills, June 12, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 1983)
  - Dinner for President Echeverria of Mexico, Pocantico Hills, June 17, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1984)
  - Benefit Cocktail Party and Supper in Behalf of Peter Peyser and Carl Vergari, Pocantico Hills, June 18, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1985)
  - Washington, D. C., National Governors' Conference, June 19-20, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1986)
  - Breakfast Meeting, 812 5th Avenue, July 26, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1987)
  - Republican National Convention, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1988)
  - Meeting with the President, November 20, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1989)
  - Cabinet Meeting, December 1, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1990)
  - Board of Regents Meeting, December 15, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1991)
  - Luncheon at St. Regis Hotel, New York City, December 18, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1992)
  - Swearing-In Ceremony and Brief Reception, Court of Appeals, December 29, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1993)
  - Swearing-In Ceremonies of Court of Appeals, December 29, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1994)
  - Delivery of Annual Message, January 3, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 1995)
  - Luncheon for the Legislators, Executive Mansion, January 3, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 1996)
  - Council of Agricultural Organizations of New York State, Red Room, January 8, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 1997)
  - New York State Community Development Committee, Conference Room, January 8, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 1998)
  - Disabled American Veterans Proclamation Signing, Red Room, January 15, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 1999)
  - Tentative Timetable for November 1973 - Referendum on Proposed Charter Revision, January 17, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2000)
  - Task Force on Financing Higher Education - Luncheon, New York City, January 18, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2001)
  - Meet with Representatives of Educational Organizations, Conference Room, January 22, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2002)
  - Press Conference on Drug Program, Red Room, January 22, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2003)
  - Reception for Emmet O'Brian, Executive Mansion, January 29, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2004)
  - Dinner, 812 5th Avenue, New York City, January 30, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2005)
  - New York Higher Education Assistance Corporation, January 31, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2006)
  - Meet with Representatives of the Council of Churches, February 5, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2007)
  - Stag Dinner in Honor of Judge Fred Young, Executive Mansion, February 5, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2008)
  - Luncheon for Empire State Chamber of Commerce Board of Directors, Executive Mansion, February 7, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2009)
  - Governors' Club Dinner Dance Honoring Governor and Mrs., February 7, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2010)
  - Legislative Reception Dinner, Executive Mansion, March 5, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2011)
  - Luncheon for the Board of Directors of Associated Industries, Executive Mansion, April 3, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2012)
  - Republican Congressional Delegation Breakfast and Dinner, April 5, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2013)
  - Private Dinner, 812 5th Avenue, April 12, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2014)
  - Public Health Council Luncheon, April 30, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2015)
  - Dinner for Mr. and Mrs. Wallace K. Harrison, Mansion, May 21, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2016)
  - Republican Governors' Conference, May 9-11, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2017)
  - Belmont Stakes, June 9, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2018)
- Nelson Rockefeller Schedule, 1958-1970; 07; 13 document box(es)
  This subseries is arranged chronologically.
  This subseries consists of Nelson Rockefeller's daily itineraries that were maintained by Diane Van Wie.
  - December 1958 (Box 67, Folder 2019)
  - January 1959 (Box 67, Folder 2020)
  - February 1959 (Box 67, Folder 2021)
  - March 1959 (Box 67, Folder 2022)
  - April 1959 (Box 67, Folder 2023)
  - May 1959 (Box 67, Folder 2024)
  - June 1959 (Box 67, Folder 2025)
  - July 1959 (Box 67, Folder 2026)
  - August 1959 (Box 67, Folder 2027)
  - September 1959 (Box 67, Folder 2028)
  - October 1959 (Box 67, Folder 2029)
  - November 1959 (Box 67, Folder 2030)
  - December 1959 (Box 68, Folder 2031)
  - January 1960 (Box 68, Folder 2032)
  - February 1960 (Box 68, Folder 2033)
  - March 1960 (Box 68, Folder 2034)
  - April 1960 (Box 68, Folder 2035)
  - May 1960 (Box 68, Folder 2036)
  - June 1960 (Box 68, Folder 2037)
  - July 1960 (Box 68, Folder 2038)
  - August 1960 (Box 68, Folder 2039)
  - September 1960 (Box 68, Folder 2040)
  - October 1960 (Box 68, Folder 2041)
  - November 1960 (Box 68, Folder 2042)
  - December 1960 (Box 69, Folder 2043)
  - January 1961 (Box 69, Folder 2044)
  - February 1961 (Box 69, Folder 2045)
  - March 1961 (Box 69, Folder 2046)
  - April 1961 (Box 69, Folder 2047)
  - May 1961 (Box 69, Folder 2048)
  - June 1961 (Box 69, Folder 2049)
  - July 1961 (Box 70, Folder 2050)
  - August 1961 (Box 70, Folder 2051)
  - September 1961 (Box 70, Folder 2052)
  - October 1961 (Box 70, Folder 2053)
  - November 1961 (Box 70, Folder 2054)
  - December 1961 (Box 70, Folder 2055)
  - January 1962 (Box 70, Folder 2056)
  - February 1962 (Box 70, Folder 2057)
  - March 1962 (Box 70, Folder 2058)
  - April 1962 (Box 70, Folder 2059)
  - May 1962 (Box 71, Folder 2060)
  - June 1962 (Box 71, Folder 2061)
  - July 1962 (Box 71, Folder 2062)
  - August 1962 (Box 71, Folder 2063)
  - September 1962 (Box 71, Folder 2064)
  - October 1962 (Box 71, Folder 2065)
  - November 1962 (Box 71, Folder 2066)
  - December 1962 (Box 71, Folder 2067)
  - January 1963 (Box 71, Folder 2068)
  - February 1963 (Box 72, Folder 2069)
  - March 1963 (Box 72, Folder 2070)
  - April 1963 (Box 72, Folder 2071)
  - May 1963 (Box 72, Folder 2072)
  - June 1963 (Box 72, Folder 2073)
  - July 1963 (Box 72, Folder 2074)
  - August 1963 (Box 72, Folder 2075)
  - September 1963 (Box 72, Folder 2076)
  - October 1963 (Box 72, Folder 2077)
  - November 1963 (Box 72, Folder 2078)
  - December 1963 (Box 72, Folder 2079)
  - January 1964 (Box 73, Folder 2080)
  - February 1964 (Box 73, Folder 2081)
  - March 1964 (Box 73, Folder 2082)
  - April 1964 (Box 73, Folder 2083)
  - May 1964 (Box 73, Folder 2084)
  - June 1964 (Box 73, Folder 2085)
  - July 1964 (Box 73, Folder 2086)
  - August 1964 (Box 73, Folder 2087)
  - September 1964 (Box 73, Folder 2088)
  - October 1964 (Box 73, Folder 2089)
  - November 1964 (Box 73, Folder 2090)
  - December 1964 (Box 74, Folder 2091)
  - January 1965 (Box 74, Folder 2092)
  - February 1965 (Box 74, Folder 2093)
  - March 1965 (Box 74, Folder 2094)
  - April 1965 (Box 74, Folder 2095)
  - May 1965 (Box 74, Folder 2096)
  - June 1965 (Box 74, Folder 2097)
  - July 1965 (Box 74, Folder 2098)
  - August 1965 (Box 74, Folder 2099)
  - Not Used (Box 74, Folder 2100-2999)
  - September 1965 (Box 74, Folder 3000)
  - October 1965 (Box 75, Folder 3001)
  - November 1965 (Box 75, Folder 3002)
  - December 1965 (Box 75, Folder 3003)
  - January 1966 (Box 75, Folder 3004)
  - February 1966 (Box 75, Folder 3005)
  - March 1966 (Box 75, Folder 3006)
  - April 1966 (Box 75, Folder 3007)
  - May 1966 (Box 76, Folder 3008)
  - June 1966 (Box 76, Folder 3009)
  - July 1966 (Box 76, Folder 3010)
  - August 1966 (Box 76, Folder 3011)
  - September 1966 (Box 76, Folder 3012)
  - October 1966 (Box 76, Folder 3013)
  - October 1966 (Box 77, Folder 3014)
  - November 1966 (Box 77, Folder 3015)
  - December 1966 (Box 77, Folder 3016)
  - January 1967 (Box 77, Folder 3017)
  - February 1967 (Box 77, Folder 3018)
  - March 1967 (Box 77, Folder 3019)
  - April 1967 (Box 77, Folder 3020)
  - May 1967 (Box 77, Folder 3021)
  - June 1967 (Box 77, Folder 3022)
  - July 1967 (Box 77, Folder 3023)
  - August 1967 (Box 77, Folder 3024)
  - September 1967 (Box 77, Folder 3025)
  - October 1967 (Box 77, Folder 3026)
  - November 1967 (Box 78, Folder 3027)
  - December 1967 (Box 78, Folder 3028)
  - January 1968 (Box 78, Folder 3029)
  - February 1968 (Box 78, Folder 3030)
  - March 1968 (Box 78, Folder 3031)
  - April 1968 (Box 78, Folder 3032)
  - May 1968 (Box 78, Folder 3033)
  - June 1968 (Box 78, Folder 3034)
  - July 1968 (Box 78, Folder 3035)
  - August 1968 (Box 78, Folder 3036)
  - September 1968 (Box 78, Folder 3037)
  - October 1968 (Box 78, Folder 3038)
  - November 1968 (Box 78, Folder 3039)
  - December 1968 (Box 78, Folder 3040)
  - January 1970 (Box 78, Folder 3041)
  - February 1970 (Box 78, Folder 3042)
  - March 1970 (Box 78, Folder 3043)
  - April 1970 (Box 79, Folder 3044)
  - May 1970 (Box 79, Folder 3045)
  - June 1970 (Box 79, Folder 3046)
  - July 1970 (Box 79, Folder 3047)
  - August 1970 (Box 79, Folder 3048)
  - September 1970 (Box 79, Folder 3049)
  - October 1970 (Box 79, Folder 3050)
  - November 1970 (Box 79, Folder 3051)
  - December 1970 (Box 79, Folder 3052)
- Position Papers and Policy Proposals, 1959-1964; 08; 16 document box(es)
  This subseries is arranged alphabetically through Box 86. Thereafter, the categories are arranged chronologically and by volume number.
  This subseries contains background papers on international and national issues and significant policies such as arms control, civil defense, foreign aid, and Latin America.
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Africa: Problems, Opportunities and Tasks. Coleman, 1960; #1 (Box 80, Folder 3053)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Union of South Africa in a Ten-Year Perspective. Carter, 1960; #2 (Box 80, Folder 3054)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Position Paper - Africa - General, 1960; #3 (Box 80, Folder 3055)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Comparison of Republican and Democratic Platforms, 1960; #4 (Box 80, Folder 3056)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Nigeria, 1961; #5 (Box 80, Folder 3057)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Summary of the Ashby Commission Report, Education in Nigeria, 1960; #6 (Box 80, Folder 3058)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Tanganyika: Education, Present and Future, 1961; #7 (Box 80, Folder 3059)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - The Sudan, 1961; #8 (Box 80, Folder 3060)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Togo, 1962; #9 (Box 80, Folder 3061)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Morocco, 1962; #10 (Box 80, Folder 3062)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Julius Nyerere of Tanganyika, 1963; #11 (Box 80, Folder 3063)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Federation of Rhodesia and Nyasaland, 1963; #12 (Box 80, Folder 3064)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Cameroun, 1963; #13 (Box 80, Folder 3065)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Proposals for American Foreign Policy Toward Africa, 1963; #14 (Box 80, Folder 3066)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - East-West Rivalry in Somalia, 1963; #15 (Box 80, Folder 3067)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Zanzibar, 1964; #16 (Box 80, Folder 3068)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Position Paper, 1964; #17 (Box 80, Folder 3069)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Interviews with Ed Draper and Waldemar Nielson, 1964; #18 (Box 80, Folder 3070)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Fact Sheet - Zanzibar, the Extent of the Communist Threat, 1964; #19 (Box 80, Folder 3071)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Zanzibar, 1964; #20 (Box 80, Folder 3072)
  - Africa Volume 9 - Background Paper - Aid to Africa, 1964; #21 (Box 80, Folder 3073)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament - Background Paper - Arms Control and Mililtary Strategy. Kelly, 1960; #1 (Box 81, Folder 3074)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament - Background Paper - Arms Control Negotiations. Sullivan, 1960; #2 (Box 81, Folder 3075)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament - Background Paper - Control of Arms. Leghorn, 1960; #3 (Box 81, Folder 3076)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament - NAR Statement - Article in "Foreign Affairs", 1960; #4 (Box 81, Folder 3077)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament - Background Paper - Summary on Arms Control. Bailey, 1960; #5 (Box 81, Folder 3078)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament - Position Paper - Arms Control - General, 1960; #6 (Box 81, Folder 3079)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament - NAR Statement - The Problems of Arms and Arms Control, 1960; #7 (Box 81, Folder 3080)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament - Background Paper - Summary of Fall 1960 Daedalus Issue, #8 (Box 81, Folder 3081)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament - Background Paper - The Available Choices in Major Arms Control Policy Questions, 1960; #10 (Box 81, Folder 3083)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament - Background Paper - Comparison of Republican and Democratic Platforms, Arms Control, 1960; #9 (Box 81, Folder 3082)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Position Paper - Arms Control - General, 1962; #11 (Box 81, Folder 3084)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Background Paper - Arms Control Policy, 1962; #12 (Box 81, Folder 3085)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Background Paper - Report No. 1 - Summary of Arms Control, 1961-1962; #13 (Box 81, Folder 3086)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Background Paper - Goldwater Position on Disarmament, 1962; #14 (Box 81, Folder 3087)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Position Paper - Arms Control - General, 1962; #15 (Box 81, Folder 3088)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Summary of NAR Proposals - Arms Control, 1963; #16 (Box 81, Folder 3089)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Position Paper - Arms Control - General, 1963; #17 (Box 81, Folder 3090)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Position Paper - Administration Proposal to Burn B-47's, 1964; #18 (Box 81, Folder 3091)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Platform Analysis Notebook - Arms Control, 1964; #19 (Box 81, Folder 3092)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Kuchel Memorandum Analysis - Arms Control, 1964; #20 (Box 81, Folder 3093)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Background Paper - Summary of Phoenix Study, 1964; #21 (Box 81, Folder 3094)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Draft Platform Planks, 1964; #22 (Box 81, Folder 3095)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Draft Platform Planks Revised, 1964; #23 (Box 81, Folder 3096)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Background Paper - Academic Proposals for Arms Control and Disarmament, 1964; #24 (Box 81, Folder 3097)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - Models Platform Planks, 1964; #25 (Box 81, Folder 3098)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Volume 11 - NAR Suggestions for Platform Committee, 1964; #26 (Box 81, Folder 3099)
  - Civil Defense Volume 12 - Background Paper - Comparison of Republican and Democratic Platforms, 1960; #1 (Box 82, Folder 3100)
  - Civil Defense Volume 12 - Background Paper - Civil Defense Report no. 2, 1960; #2 (Box 82, Folder 3101)
  - Civil Defense Volume 12 - Questions and Answers for NAR TV Appearance, 1962; #3 (Box 82, Folder 3102)
  - Civil Defense Volume 12 - Position Paper - Civil Defense - General, 1962; #4 (Box 82, Folder 3103)
  - Civil Defense Volume 12 - Background Paper - Civil Defense Report no. 3, 1962; #5 (Box 82, Folder 3104)
  - Civil Defense Volume 12 - Position Paper - Civil Defense - General, 1962; #6 (Box 82, Folder 3105)
  - Civil Defense Volume 12 - Background Paper - Civil Defense Report no. 4, 1962; #7 (Box 82, Folder 3106)
  - Civil Defense Volume 12 - Position Paper - Civil Defense - General, 1962; #8 (Box 82, Folder 3107)
  - Civil Defense Volume 12 - Position Paper - Civil Defense - General, 1962; #9 (Box 82, Folder 3108)
  - Civil Defense Volume 12 - Current Position Cards - Civil Defense, 1962; #10 (Box 82, Folder 3109)
  - Civil Defense Volume 12 - Summary of NAR Proposals - Civil Defense, 1962; #11 (Box 82, Folder 3110)
  - Civil Defense Volume 12 - Position Paper - Civil Defense Bill, 1964; #12 (Box 82, Folder 3111)
  - Confederations Volume 13, 1959-1960; #1-2 (Box 82, Folder 3112)
  - Confederations Volume 13, 1960; #1-15 (Box 82, Folder 3113)
  - Confederations Volume 13, 1960-1961; #16-27 (Box 82, Folder 3114)
  - Cuba Volume 14, 1961-1964; #1-15 (Box 82, Folder 3115)
  - Cuba Volume 14, 1961-1964; #16-34 (Box 82, Folder 3116)
  - Defense Volume 16, 1961-1964; #12-15 (Box 82, Folder 3117)
  - Defense Volume 16, 1961-1964; #16-21 (Box 83, Folder 3118)
  - Defense Volume 16, 1961-1964; #22 (Box 83, Folder 3119)
  - Defense Volume 16, 1961-1964; #23-33 (Box 83, Folder 3120)
  - Foreign Aid Volume 18, 1959-1960; #1 (Box 83, Folder 3121)
  - Foreign Aid Volume 18, 1959-1960; #2 (Box 83, Folder 3122)
  - Foreign Aid Volume 18, 1959-1960; #3 (Box 83, Folder 3123)
  - Foreign Aid Volume 18, 1959-1960; #4-7 (Box 83, Folder 3124)
  - Foreign Aid Volume 19, 1961-1964; #8-20 (Box 83, Folder 3125)
  - Foreign Aid Volume 19, 1961-1964; #21-35 (Box 83, Folder 3126)
  - Latin America Volume 20, 1959-1960; #1-6 (Box 84, Folder 3127)
  - Latin America Volume 20, 1959-1960; #7-9 (Box 84, Folder 3128)
  - Latin America Volume 20, 1961-1964; #10-21 (Box 84, Folder 3129)
  - Middle East Volume 22, 1959-1960; #1-4 (Box 84, Folder 3130)
  - Middle East Volume 22, 1961-1964; #5-15 (Box 84, Folder 3131)
  - Middle East Volume 22, 1961-1964; #16-22 (Box 84, Folder 3132)
  - Southeast Asia Volume 26, 1961-1964; #19-41 (Box 85, Folder 3133)
  - Southeast Asia Volume 26, 1961-1964; #42-60 (Box 85, Folder 3134)
  - Southeast Asia Volume 26, 1961-1964; #61-76 (Box 85, Folder 3135)
  - Western Europe Volume 31, 1963-1964; #18 (Box 85, Folder 3136)
  - Western Europe Volume 31, 1963-1964; #19 (Box 85, Folder 3137)
  - Western Europe Volume 31, 1963-1964; #20 (Box 85, Folder 3138)
  - Western Europe Volume 31, 1963-1964; #21-30 (Box 85, Folder 3139)
  - Western Europe Volume 31, 1963-1964; #31-39 (Box 85, Folder 3140)
  - Natural Resources and Power Volume 49, 1959-1960; #18-24 (Box 86, Folder 3141)
  - Natural Resources and Power Volume 49, 1959-1960; #25-35 (Box 86, Folder 3142)
  - Natural Resources and Power Volume 49, 1959-1960; #36-55 (Box 86, Folder 3143)
  - Natural Resources and Power Volume 49, 1959-1960; #56-81 (Box 86, Folder 3144)
  - Transportation Volume 50, 1959-1960; #1-10 (Box 86, Folder 3145)
  - Transportation Volume 50, 1961-1964; #11-25 (Box 86, Folder 3146)
  - Transportation Volume 50, 1961-1964; #26-41 (Box 87, Folder 3147)
  - Housing and Urban Affairs Volume 51 + 52, 1959-1960; #1-8 (Box 87, Folder 3148)
  - Housing and Urban Affairs Volume 51 + 52, 1959-1960; #9-25 (Box 87, Folder 3149)
  - Housing and Urban Affairs Volume 51 + 52, 1961-1964; #26-47 (Box 87, Folder 3150)
  - Welfare Volume 53, 1961-1964; #1-15 (Box 87, Folder 3151)
  - Welfare Volume 53, 1961-1964; #16-30 (Box 87, Folder 3152)
  - Welfare Volume 53, 1961-1964; #31-47 (Box 87, Folder 3153)
  - Additional Categories Volume 54, 1961-1964; #1-15 (Box 88, Folder 3154)
  - Additional Categories Volume 54, 1961-1964; #16-49 (Box 88, Folder 3155)
  - Additional Categories Volume 54, 1961-1964; #50-63 (Box 88, Folder 3156)
  - Additional Categories Volume 54, 1961-1964; #64-79 (Box 88, Folder 3157)
  - State Books Volume 56, 1959-1960; #1-3 (Box 88, Folder 3158)
  - State Books Volume 56, 1959-1960; #4-5 (Box 88, Folder 3159)
  - State Books Volume 57, 1959-1960; #6-7 (Box 89, Folder 3160)
  - State Books Volume 57, 1959-1960; #8-9 (Box 89, Folder 3161)
  - State Books Volume 57, 1959-1960; #10-12 (Box 89, Folder 3162)
  - State Books Volume 58, 1959-1960; #13-16 (Box 89, Folder 3163)
  - State Books Volume 58, 1959-1960; #17-20 (Box 89, Folder 3164)
  - State Books Volume 59, 1961-1964; #21-27 (Box 89, Folder 3165)
  - State Books Volume 59, 1961-1964; #28 (Box 89, Folder 3166)
  - State Books Volume 59, 1961-1964; #29 (Box 89, Folder 3167)
  - State Books Volume 60, 1961-1964; #30 (Box 90, Folder 3168)
  - Goldwater General Volume 61, 1961-1964; #1-8 (Box 90, Folder 3169)
  - Goldwater General Volume 61, 1961-1964; #9-24 (Box 90, Folder 3170)
  - Goldwater General Volume 62, 1961-1964; #25-36 (Box 90, Folder 3171)
  - Goldwater General Volume 62, 1961-1964; #37-40 (Box 90, Folder 3172)
  - Goldwater General Volume 62, 1961-1964; #41-56 (Box 90, Folder 3173)
  - Goldwater General Volume 63, 1961-1964; #57-58 (Box 90, Folder 3174)
  - Goldwater General Volume 63, 1961-1964; #59 (Box 90, Folder 3175)
  - Goldwater General Volume 63, 1961-1964; #60-66 (Box 91, Folder 3176)
  - Goldwater General Volume 63, 1961-1964; #67 (Box 91, Folder 3177)
  - Goldwater Foreign Volume 64 - Foreign - China, 1961-1964; #1-5 (Box 91, Folder 3178)
  - Goldwater General Volume 64 - Foreign - Cuba, 1961-1964; #6-20 (Box 91, Folder 3179)
  - Goldwater General Volume 64 - Foreign - Defense, 1961-1964; #21-34 (Box 91, Folder 3180)
  - Goldwater General Volume 64 - Foreign - Aid, 1961-1964; #35-52 (Box 91, Folder 3181)
  - Goldwater General Volume 64 - Foreign - Nuclear Weapons, 1961-1964; #53-83 (Box 91, Folder 3182)
  - Goldwater General Volume 64 - Foreign - United Nations, 1961-1964; #84-122 (Box 91, Folder 3183)
  - Goldwater General Volume 64 - Foreign - Withdrawals of Recognition from Russia, 1961-1964; #123-138 (Box 91, Folder 3184)
  - Goldwater Domestic Volume 65 - Agriculture, 1961-1964; #1-12 (Box 91, Folder 3185)
  - Goldwater Domestic Volume 66 - Civil Rights, 1961-1964; #13-41 (Box 92, Folder 3186)
  - Goldwater Domestic Volume 66 - Education, 1961-1964; #42-50 (Box 92, Folder 3187)
  - Goldwater Domestic Volume 66 - Education, 1961-1964; #51-72 (Box 92, Folder 3188)
  - Goldwater Domestic Volume 66 - Health, 1961-1964; #73-84 (Box 92, Folder 3189)
  - Goldwater Domestic Volume 66 - Labor, 1961-1964; #85-109 (Box 92, Folder 3190)
  - Goldwater Domestic Volume 66 - Social Security, 1961-1964; #110-126 (Box 92, Folder 3191)
  - Goldwater Domestic Volume 66 - Taxation, 1961-1964; #127-153 (Box 92, Folder 3192)